visitvictoria.com 2014-12-04

# Privacy - Melbourne, Victoria, Australia

This online Privacy and Website Notice applies to this site, which is operated by Tourism Victoria (ABN 18 381 772 530) under the domain name 'visitvictoria.com', and other Tourism Victoria internet sites. It explains how Tourism Victoria collects, uses and manages the information of visitors to its internet sites. Tourism Victoria views the privacy of your personal information as an important issue, and is committed to protecting your privacy when you access and interact with the Tourism Victoria site. As such, this site supports and endorses the principles of the Victorian _Privacy and Data Protection Act 2014_.

Visitor logs are used on this site for statistical purposes only, and no attempt will be made to identify you or your browsing activity. This information will only be used to update and improve the site.

Email addresses will only be used to respond to specific user queries, and will not be kept or used for any purpose other than stated. Email addresses will not be added to a mailing list unless consent is given, nor disclosed to any other party without your knowledge or consent.

This Privacy and Website Notice may be updated from time to time. Tourism Victoria suggests that you return to the site on a regular basis and carefully read the information provided.

**Cookies**  
This site uses 'cookies' to make your experience of the site easier and more efficient. A cookie is a small data file placed on your hard drive by Tourism Victoria's web page server. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on a computer virus, or capture your email address. Note that the cookie will remain on your computer as a record for future visits to this website.

In using cookies, Tourism Victoria does not record any personal information, collect names or details of commercial transactions. In addition, Tourism Victoria does not use cookies as the basis for direct marketing.

You can configure your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, providing you with the opportunity to either accept or reject it. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, or delete all cookies from your computer if required.

When you visit the site, Tourism Victoria's Internet Service Provider (ISP) makes a record of your visits and logs the following information for statistical purposes – your server address, your top-level domain name, the date and time of your visit to the site, the pages accessed and documents downloaded, the previous site visited and the type of browser used.

This statement is to be read in conjunction with the rights claimed by the Privacy Act 1998 at [privacy.gov.au](http://www.privacy.gov.au/)

**Personal information** **  
** Any personal information collected through this website will only be made available to Government personnel or approved contracted parties whose duties require them to use this information. Any personal information collected through this website will also be disclosed if required by law.

If you wish to access or alter any personal information we may have collected about you, you may request such access by contacting our Privacy Officer on 03 9653 9777 during business hours. You may also contact our Privacy Officer in relation to any other concerns you may have about the privacy of personal information when using this website.

**Website usage measurement** **  
** This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ('Google').  Google Analytics uses cookies to help the website analyse how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. 

In addition to data collected through a standard Google Analytics implementation, this website uses Google Analytics Advertising Features along with DoubleClick cookies to measure demographic and interest data.

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. 

To prevent your browser data being used by Google Analytics, opt-out [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

For further information, please visit [google.com/privacy](http://www.google.com/privacy)

This website uses pixels, or transparent GIF files, to help manage online advertising. These GIF files are provided by our ad management partner, DoubleClick. These files enable DoubleClick to recognise a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie is placed by us, or by another advertiser who works with DoubleClick. With both cookies and Spotlight technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. For more information about DoubleClick, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, please visit [doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy)

The analytics cookies on our site gather anonymous data such as geographic location, the method you used to reach this site, the length of your visit, the time of your visit, the pages that you visit and the keywords used to search while on the site.  If you don’t wish us to capture this information on your visit you can opt-out [here](http://www.omniture.com/en/privacy/2o7#optout) 

Double Click for Publishers (DFP) is used to track where any ad placements are on our site, and how many times these have been viewed or clicked on by visitors.  If you don’t wish us to capture this information on your visit you can opt-out [here](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin/)  

**Internet use risks**  
Tourism Victoria does not warrant that the functions contained in the site will be uninterrupted or without error. In addition, Tourism Victoria shall not be responsible for the propagation of computer worms, viruses or other harmful components transmitted from this site and other third-party sites. 

**Quoted prices**  
Figures and/or prices stated on the Tourism Victoria site are generally prices for tourist services, such as accommodation, day tours or attraction entrance fees. All figures quoted are in Australian dollars, unless otherwise stated, and include a Goods and Services Tax (GST). Prior to making bookings, you should check the availability and price of accommodation and services with the operator, and any applicable terms and conditions.

**Trademarks**  
The 'Tourism Victoria' and the 'You'll love every piece of Victoria' name and logos are trademarks of Tourism Victoria. All rights are reserved for these logos. Logos must not be used in any form without the prior written consent of Tourism Victoria. All other trademarks appearing on the Tourism Victoria site are the property of their respective owners.

**Links to other sites**  
Where Tourism Victoria offers links to other sites, Tourism Victoria is not affiliated with those sites and has no control over, and is not responsible for, their content, privacy practice or other policies. Third-party sites should contain their own privacy notes, and those third parties should be responsible for their own privacy practices. Written requests for Tourism Victoria to link to a site should be forwarded to [Online Comments](mailto:onlinecomments@tourism.vic.gov.au)

Tourism Victoria welcomes links from other sites. Please contact [Tourism Victoria](mailto:onlinecomments@tourism.vic.gov.au) to seek written permission to link to the site.

**Editorial policy**  
The information provided on this site is posted at the discretion of Tourism Victoria. The site publishes articles, interviews and information that Tourism Victoria believes will be of interest and value. All views and opinions contained in the articles, interviews, or other information on the site are solely the opinion of the writer, and do not necessarily reflect the opinions of Tourism Victoria.
